A Guide to the Correspondence Files of Special Collections, University of Virginia Library 1931-1990s
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: Correspondence (General)
  - Manuscripts Department Correspondence [ante 1990] and Patron-Use Files (Box A28-7A through A29-17T)
    - Patron Registrations
      - Patron Registrations 1983 Jul - 1984 Jun (Box A29-14M)
      - Patron Registrations 1984 Jul - 1985 Jun (Box A29-14R)
      - Patron Registrations 1984 Jul - 1985 Jun (Box A29-14S)
        alphabetical H - Z
      - Patron Registrations 1985 Jul - 1986 Jun (Box A29-15B)
        alphabetical A - Poch
      - Patron Registrations 1985 Jul 1986 Jun (Box A29-15C)
        alphabetical Pow - Z
      - Patron Registrations 1986 Jul - 1987 Jun (Box A29-15F)
      - Patron Registrations 1987 Jul 1988 Jun (Box A29-15I)
      - Patron Registrations 1988 Jul - 1989 Jun (Box A29-15L)
        alphabetical A - K
      - Patron Registrations 1988 Jul - 1989 Jun (Box A29-15M)
        alphabetical L - Z
      - Patron Registrations 1989 Jul - 1990 Jun (Box A29-15P)
        alphabetical A - F
      - Patron Registrations 1989 Jul - 1990 Jun (Box A29-15Q)
        alphabetical G - M
      - Patron Registrations 1989 Jul - 1990 Jun (Box A29-15R)
        alphabetical N - Z
      - Patron Registrations 1990 Jul - 1991 Jun (Box A29-16A)
      - Patron Registrations 1990 Jul - 1991 Jun (Box A29-16B)
      - Patron Registrations 1990 Jul - 1991 Jun (Box A29-16C)
      - Patron Registrations 1991 Jul - 1992 Jun (Box A29-16F)
      - Patron Registrations 1991 Jul - 1992 Jun (Box A29-16G)
        alphabetical E - J
      - Patron Registrations 1991 Jul - 1992 Jun (Box A29-16H)
        alphabetical K - Q
      - Patron Registrations 1991 Jul - 1992 Jun (Box A29-16I)
        alphabetical R - Z
      - Patron Registrations 1992 Jul - 1993 Jun (Box A29-16L)
        alphabetical A - C
      - Patron Registrations 1992 Jul - 1993 Jun (Box A29-16M)
        alphabetical D - He
      - Patron Registrations 1992 Jul - 1993 Jun (Box A29-16N)
        alphabetical Hi - Mc
      - Patron Registrations 1992 Jul - 1993 Jun (Box A29-16O)
        alphabetical M - R
      - Patron Registrations 1992 Jul - 1993 Jun (Box A29-16P)
        alphabetical S - Z
      - Patron Registrations 1993 Jul - 1994 Jun (Box A29-16S)
        alphabetical A - E
      - Patron Registrations 1993 Jul - 1994 Jun (Box A29-16T)
        alphabetical F - L
      - Patron Registrations 1993 Jul - 1994 Jun (Box A29-17A)
      - Patron Registrations 1993 Jul - 1994 Jun (Box A29-17B)
      - Patron Registrations 1994 Jul - 1995 Jun (Box A29-17E)
      - Patron Registrations 1994 Jul - 1995 Jun (Box A29-17F)
      - Patron Registrations 1994 Jul - 1995 Jun (Box A29-17G)
      - Patron Registrations 1995 Jul - 1996 Jun (Box A29-17J)
      - Patron Registrations 1995 Jul - 1996 Jun (Box A29-17K)
        alphabetical G - O
      - Patron Registrations 1995 Jul - 1996 Jun (Box A29-17L)
    - Patron Daily Logbooks (Sign-in Books)
      - Patron Daily Logbooks (sign-in books) 1975 May - 1980 Jun (Box A29-17P)
      - Patron Daily Logbooks (sign-in books) 1980 Jul - 1985 Jun (Box A29-17Q)
      - Patron Daily Logbooks (sign-in books) 1985 Jul - 1990 Jun (Box A29-17R)
      - Patron Daily Logbooks (sign-in books) 1990 Jul - 1993 Jun (Box A29-17S)
      - Patron Daily Logbooks (sign-in books) 1993 Jul - 1996 Jun (Box A29-17T)
  - Special Collections Dept. Correspondence 1990-1997
    - A - General 1987-1991 (Box A36-10A)
    - Academic Computing Center (Box A36-10A)
    - Accounting Operations - Newsletter (Box A36-10A)
    - Acquisitions Correspondence (Box A36-10A)
    - Afro-Americans 1990 (Box A36-10A)
    - Air Conditioning Project (Box A36-10A)
    - Alarm System (1991- ) (Box A36-10A)
    - ACHS / Albemarle County Historical Society - Building Study Committee (Box A36-10A)
    - Alcott, Louisa May 1990-1991 (Box A36-10A)
    - Alecto Historical Editions (Box A36-10A)
    - Alfriend, Edward (Ed) (Box A36-10A)
    - American Association of University Women 1990 (Box A36-10A)
    - American Rhododendron Society (Box A36-10A)
    - Annual Reports - Library (Box A36-10A)
    - Annual Statistical Reports (1988- ) (Box A36-10A)
    - APHA Newsletter / American Printing History Association (Box A36-10A)
    - Applications (1988- ) (Box A36-10A)
    - Architectural Records - Data Sheets (blank) (Box A36-10A)
    - Archives (1990) (Box A36-10A)
    - Archives 1991 (Box A36-10B)
    - Arnold, Matthew 1990-1991 (Box A36-10B)
    - Associates of the University of Virginia Library 1990 (Box A36-10B)
    - B - General (Rare Books only) 1987-1988 (Box A36-10B)
    - B - General (MSS & RBR) 1989-1991 (Box A36-10B)
    - Balch Family 1990 (Box A36-10B)
    - Barrett Library - Lent material problem, (1989 summer-fall; 1980 Jul - 1981 Jun) (Box A36-10B)
    - Barrett Volunteers Program (see also Ann Freudenberg's file) 1989-1990 (Box A36-10B)
    - Berkeley Family 1990-1991 (Box A36-10B)
    - Bibliographical Society of University of Virginia (Box A36-10B)
    - Biennial Evaluation & Planning Report 1984-1998 (Box A36-10C)
    - Bierce (1990- ) (Box A36-10C)
    - Binding Budget (Box A36-10C)
    - University of Virginia Board of Visitors - Building Committee (Box A36-10C)
    - Book Appraisal Fair (Associates) (Box A36-10C)
    - Book Arts Press (Box A36-10C)
    - Book Funds - Report (Box A36-10C)
    - Bond, Julian 1989-1991 (Box A36-10C)
    - Bowles, Paul 1989-1991 (Box A36-10C)
    - Brick Row Bookshop (Box A36-10C)
    - Bruccoli, Matthew / Manly Associates Inc./ Bruccoli-Clark Layman 1990-1991 (Box A36-10D)
    - Budget / Students / Payroll Sheets 1991-1992 (Box A36-10D)
    - Budget, FY: Binding 1990-1992 (Box A36-10D)
    - Budget, FY: Book Funds 1991-1992 (Box A36-10D)
    - Budget, FY: Equipment 1990-1992 (Box A36-10D)
    - Budget, FY 1990-1992: General 1990-1992 (Box A36-10D)
    - Budget, FY: Travel 1991-1992 (Box A36-10D)
    - Business - Manuscripts Division 1991 (Box A36-10D)
    - Byrd, Harry F., Jr. 1989-1991 (Box A36-10D)
    - Byrd, Harry F., Sr. 1989-1992 (Box A36-10D)
    - Byrd - Permissions ( -1991) (Box A36-10D)
    - Byrd - Permissions (Box A36-10E)
    - C - General - Rare Books (1987-1989) (Box A36-10E)
    - C - General - MSS & RBR (1990-1991) (Box A36-10E)
    - Cabell, James Branch 1991 (Box A36-10E)
    - Carter G. Woodson Institute 1990 (Box A36-10E)
    - Carter, Robert "King" 1989 (Box A36-10E)
    - Cartoons (1990- ) (Box A36-10E)
    - Casey, John / Pancake 1990-1992 (Box A36-10E)
    - Central American Indian Languages Collection (1990- ) (Box A36-10F)
    - Chadwyck-Healey Inc. / Natl. Inventory of Doc. Sources (1990- ) (Box A36-10F)
    - Cather, Willa (1990- ) (Box A36-10F)
    - Chappell, Warren 1990-1991 (Box A36-10F)
    - Check Distribution Representatives (Box A36-10F)
    - Cheuse, Alan (1990-1993) (Box A36-10F)
    - Childs, J. Rives (1990- ) (Box A36-10F)
    - Church Records 1990-1992 (Box A36-10F)
    - Civil War 1990-1991 (Box A36-10F)
    - Clay, Henry 1990-1991 (Box A36-10F)
    - Cocke Family 1990-1992 (Box A36-10F)
    - Cocke Papers - Elliot, John Page 1990-1991 (Box A36-10F)
    - Collection Development (Box A36-10F)
    - Colonial Dames (Box A36-10F)
    - Colonial Williamsburg 1990-1991 (Box A36-10F)
    - The Commission on Preservation and Access (Box A36-10F)
    - Conservation 1992 (Box A36-10G)
    - Conservation Center for Art and Historical Artifacts 1990-1992 (Box A36-10G)
    - Conservation Center (Box A36-10G)
    - Coolidge, Harold Jefferson 1990-1991 (Box A36-10G)
    - Crane, Stephen 1990-1992 (Box A36-10G)
    - Cummings, Homer S. 1990-1991 (Box A36-10G)
    - D - General 1990 (Box A36-10G)
    - D - General - MSS & RBR 1987-1991 (Box A36-10G)
    - Dabney, Virginius 1990-1992 (Box A36-10G)
    - Daniel, John Warwick 1990-1992 (Box A36-10G)
    - Daughters of the American Revolution 1990 (Box A36-10G)
    - Davis, Jefferson 1989-1990 (Box A36-10G)
    - Davis, Rebecca Harding 1990-1991 (Box A36-10G)
    - Davis, Richard Harding 1989-1992 (Box A36-10G)
    - Dealers - Manuscripts (Box A36-10G)
    - Dealers 1990-1991 (Box A36-10G)
    - Declaration of Independence (Box A36-10G)
    - Dew, Charles and Robb 1990 (Box A36-10G)
    - SCD - Director's Correspondence 1990-1992 (Box A36-10H)
    - Director's Council (Box A36-10H)
    - Doris, Virginia 1990 (Box A36-10H)
    - Dos Passos, John 1990-1991 (Box A36-10H)
    - E - General - MSS & RBR 1987-1991 (Box A36-10H)
    - Edgehill-Randolph Family 1990-1991 (Box A36-10H)
    - Eisenhart, Mr. & Mrs. Edward C. / Charles Fund (Box A36-10H)
    - Eliot, T.S. 1990-1991 (Box A36-10H)
    - Eppes, William D. 1990-1991 (Box A36-10H)
    - Ergonomics (Box A36-10H)
    - Equipment (1990- ) (Box A36-10H)
    - Exhibits - Miniature Books 1992 April (Box A36-10I)
    - Exhibits - St. Gall 1992 June-July (Box A36-10I)
    - Swiss Exhibition (Box A36-10I)
    - F - General - MSS & RBR 1987-1991 (Box A36-10I)
    - Faculty Information - Memos, notices received, etc. (Box A36-10I)
    - Faculty Meetings - S.C. Dept. (Box A36-10I)
    - Faulkner, William 1990-1991 (Box A36-10I)
    - Faulkner - Garland 1989-1990 (Box A36-10I)
    - Faulkner, William - Mosquitoes #6074-o 1989-1991 (Box A36-10I)
    - Faulkner, William - "Vision in Spring" 1990 (Box A36-10I)
    - Flakne, Joseph (Box A36-10I)
    - Folklore 1990-1991 (Box A36-10I)
    - Frost, Robert 1990-1991 (Box A36-10I)
    - G - General - MSS & RBR 1987-1991 (Box A36-10J)
    - Garrett, George 1990 (Box A36-10J)
    - Genealogy 1990-1991 (Box A36-10J)
    - General Fac. Council (Box A36-10J)
    - Gift File 1991 (Box A36-10J)
    - Gilmer Family 1990 (Box A36-10J)
    - Glasgow, Ellen 1990-1992 (Box A36-10J)
    - Glaspell, Susan 1990-1991 (Box A36-10J)
    - Goals & Objectives (Box A36-10J)
    - Gordon, Douglas H. (Box A36-10K)
    - Gordon, Douglas H. - Books in the Charlecote House Library 1980-1981 (Box A36-10K)
    - Gordon - Diderot - Encyclopedie (Box A36-10K)
    - Gordon (Box A36-10K)
    - Gordon, Douglas Huntly - will of (Box A36-10K)
    - Gordon - Ephemera (Box A36-10K)
    - Graham Collection / Agnes Graham Sanders Riley 1990-1992 (Box A36-10K)
    - Grumbach, Doris 1989-1992 (Box A36-10K)
    - H - General - RBR 1987-1991 (Box A36-10K)
    - H - General - MSS 1990-1991 (Box A36-10K)
    - Halle, Louis J. 1990-1991 (Box A36-10L)
    - Harris, Angela (Box A36-10L)
    - Hawthorne, Nathaniel 1988-1992 (Box A36-10L)
    - Hearn, Lafcadio 1990-1991 (Box A36-10L)
    - Hemingway, Ernest 1990-1991 (Box A36-10L)
    - Hench, Atcheson L. 1990-1991 (Box A36-10L)
    - Henkel Family 1989-1991 (Box A36-10L)
    - Holsinger 1991 (Box A36-10L)
    - Holsinger Studio 1990 (Box A36-10L)
    - Hopper, Mrs. Rea - Va. Assoc. broadside (Box A36-10L)
    - Hoy, Peter 1990 (Box A36-10L)
    - I - General - MSS & RBR (1988- ) (Box A36-10L)
    - Incunabula Short Title Catalog (Box A36-10L)
    - Interlibrary Loans - Xerox orders 1990 (Box A36-10L)
    - J - General - MSS & RBR 1988-1991 (Box A36-10L)
    - James, Henry / James, William / James Family 1990-1991 (Box A36-10L)
    - Papers of John Janney 1990 (Box A36-10L)
    - Jefferson, Isaac 1991 (Box A36-10L)
    - Jefferson - Ciphers 1990-1991 (Box A36-10L)
    - Jefferson Drawings July 1990 - June 1991 (Box A36-10L)
    - Jefferson Drawings Jan-Jun 1990 (Box A36-10M)
    - Jefferson Drawings Jul-Dec 1991 (Box A36-10M)
    - Jefferson - Engravings (1990-1991) (Box A36-10M)
    - Jefferson - Facsimile - Correspondence 1990 (Box A36-10M)
    - Jefferson 1990-1991 (Box A36-10M)
    - Jefferson - Music 1990-1991 (Box A36-10M)
    - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation 1990-1991 (Box A36-10M)
    - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Fund (Box A36-10M)
    - Jefferson - Poplar Forest 1990-1992 (Box A36-10M)
    - Jefferson Portraits & Paintings & Statues 1990-1991 (Box A36-10M)
    - Jefferson - Royalty Payment, Commissions 1990 (Box A36-10M)
    - Papers of Thomas Jefferson, Princeton University Library 1990-1991 (Box A36-10M)
    - K - General - MSS & RBR 1987-1991 (Box A36-10N)
    - Keepsakes (Box A36-10N)
    - Kilpatrick, James Jackson 1990-1992 (Box A36-10N)
    - L - General -MSS & RBR 1987-1991 (Box A36-10N)
    - Lauck Papers (1990- ) (Box A36-10N)
    - Lay, K. Edward 1990-1992 (Box A36-10N)
    - Leave Representatives (Box A36-10N)
    - Leaves & Nine-month Contracts (Box A36-10N)
    - Lee Family Papers 1990-1992 (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Automation Planning Group (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Biennial Evaluation & Planning Report 1984-1998 (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Bibliographic Records Services (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Bibliographic Records Services - Unit Head Minutes (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Black History Month Task Force (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Cataloging Services (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Circulation Department (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Claude Moore Health Sciences Automation Planning Group (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Clemons Library Staff Meetings (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Collection Development Group (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Committee on Document Delivery (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Electronic Information Services Committee (folder empty) (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Ethernet (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Faculty Advisory Committee (folder empty) (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Faculty Council (folder empty) (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Faculty Performance Evaluations Committee (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Faculty Promotions Committee (folder empty) (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Faculty Research Commitee (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Fine Arts (Fiske Kimball Library) (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Information Services Group (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Innovacq (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Integrated Systems Planning (folder empty) (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Kardex (Box A36-10N)
    - Library Assistant Class Review 1989-1990 (Box A36-10N)
    - Library: Manuscripts Faculty Meetings (folder empty) (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: Materials Organization Group (folder empty) (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: M.D.A.S. Committee (folder empty) (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: Multicultural Issues Committee (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: Organization Committee (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: Personnel Issues & Staff Development Committee (folder empty) (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: Planning Committee (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: Publications Committee (folder empty) (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: Purchase of Materials (folder empty) (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: Reference Dept. (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: Resources Distribution (folder empty) (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: Safety & Emergencies (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: Science & Engineering (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: Search Committee for Information Services Librarian (Box A36-10O)
    - Solinet Preservation Advisory Committee (folder empty) (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: Special Collections Acquisitions Group (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: Special Collections Minutes (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: Staff Association (folder empty) (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: Staff Sharing Program (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: State Book Funds Expenditure Analysis (folder empty) (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: Student Library Employees Committee (folder empty) (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: Sub-Committee on Closing the Card Catalog (folder empty) (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: Sub-Committee: Holdings Information (folder empty) (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: Systems Planning (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: User Education Committee (folder empty) (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: V.A.S.T. (Box A36-10O)
    - Library: Virgo (Box A36-10O)
    - Lindsay, Vachel 1990 (Box A36-10O)
    - Loans Correspondence & Returns, Virginia Museum of Fine Art 1990-1992 (Box A36-10O)
    - I.L.L. requests filled by Xeroxing 1990-1992 (Box A36-10O)
    - Loans, Correspondence, Receipts 1991 (Box A36-10O)
    - Loans Returned - Greg 1990 (Box A36-10O)
    - Loans - Greg 1991-1992 (Box A36-10P)
    - LSU / Louisiana State University (Box A36-10P)
    - M - General - RBR 1987-1989 (Box A36-10P)
    - M - General - MSS & RBR 1990-1991 (Box A36-10P)
    - Madison, James 1990-1991 (Box A36-10P)
    - Madison, James - National Trust for Historic Preservation 1990-1991 (Box A36-10P)
    - Manarin, Louis H. 1990-1991 (Box A36-10P)
    - Manuscript Volunteers 1990 (Box A36-10P)
    - Manuscripts Society 1990 (Box A36-10P)
    - MAP Questionnaire (Box A36-10P)
    - Massey, John W. (Box A36-10P)
    - Masters, Edgar Lee 1990-1991 (Box A36-10P)
    - Maupin, Socrates (1990- ) (Box A36-10P)
    - Maury-Fontaine Papers 1990-1992 (Box A36-10P)
    - Mc - General (Box A36-10P)
    - McGehee, Mrs. C. Coleman (Box A36-10P)
    - Memos (1990- ) (Box A36-10P)
    - Hillis Fry McLemore Collection 1990-1991 (Box A36-10P)
    - Memoranda - Departmental Leave (Box A36-10P)
    - Memoranda - Incoming from General Office 1992-1993 (Box A36-10P)
    - Memoranda - Incoming from General Office 1990-1992 (Box A36-10Q)
    - Memoranda - Outgoing 1990-1992 (Box A36-10Q)
    - Memoranda - Within Department (Internal) (Box A36-10Q)
    - Miller, Henry 1990-1991 (Box A36-10Q)
    - Miller School 1990 (Box A36-10Q)
    - Misc. Library Information (1992- ) (Box A36-10Q)
    - Misc. Meetings 1992 (Box A36-10Q)
    - Mold-Mildew Problem (1991- ) (Box A36-10Q)
    - Monroe, James 1990-1991 (Box A36-10Q)
    - Moore, John Travers ( -1994) (Box A36-10Q)
    - Moran, Charles E., Jr. (1990- ) (Box A36-10Q)
    - Morganthau, Hans 1990-1991 (Box A36-10Q)
    - Mosby, John 1990-1991 (Box A36-10Q)
    - Museum of the Confederacy 1990-1992 (Box A36-10Q)
    - Mussey, Mrs. Barrows (Box A36-10Q)
    - N - General - MSS & RBR 1987-1991 (Box A36-10R)
    - NHPRC - Archives Administration Fellow Grant Project 1990 (Box A36-10R)
    - National Portrait Gallery (1991- ) (Box A36-10R)
    - North Anna Power Station - U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission 1990-1991 (Box A36-10R)
    - Notis (Box A36-10R)
    - O - General - MSS & RBR (1987- ) (Box A36-10R)
    - Offprints (Box A36-10R)
    - O'Keeffe, Georgia 1990 (Box A36-10R)
    - O'Keeffe, Richard 1990-1992 (Box A36-10R)
    - P - General - MSS & RBR 1987-1991 (Box A36-10R)
    - Page, Thomas Nelson 1990 (Box A36-10R)
    - Perdue, Kevin Barry Archives 1990 (Box A36-10R)
    - Personnel (Box A36-10R)
    - Planned Giving (Box A36-10R)
    - Planning Day 1992 (Box A36-10R)
    - Plantation Records - Ante Bellum Southern Plantations (Box A36-10R)
    - Poe, Edgar Allan / Poe-Ingram 1990-1991 (Box A36-10R)
    - Poe 1990 (Box A36-10R)
    - Poe-Ingram Papers 1990 (Box A36-10R)
    - Policies - General (Box A36-10R)
    - Pope, Alexander (Box A36-10R)
    - Postal Information (Box A36-10R)
    - Pound, Ezra (1990- ) (Box A36-10R)
    - Powell, John 1990-1992 (Box A36-10R)
    - Presentations - Thank Yous 1991 (Box A36-10R)
    - Presidents Office (Box A36-10R)
    - Printing Orders (Box A36-10S)
    - Procedures File (Box A36-10S)
    - Processing Costs FY 1989/1990 - FY 1992/1993 (Box A36-10S)
    - Public Service Questionnaire (folder 1 of 2) Mar-May 1992 (Box A36-10S)
    - Public Service Questionnaire (folder 2 of 2) Mar-May 1992 (Box A36-10T)
    - Public Service - Special Collections Staff (folder empty) (Box A36-10T)
    - Publication Agreements (Box A36-10T)
    - Publication Agreements 1990-1991 (Box A36-10T)
    - Publicity - News Releases - Commendations 1990 (Box A36-10T)
    - Purchase Proposals 1990-1992 (Box A36-10T)
    - Q - General (Box A36-10T)
    - Q - General 1990 (Box A36-10T)
    - Questionnaires (Box A36-10T)
    - R - General - MSS 1991 (Box A36-10T)
    - R - General - MSS & RBR 1987-1990 (Box A36-10T)
    - Randolph Family 1990,1992 (Box A36-11A)
    - Randolph, John (of Roanoke) 1990-1991 (Box A36-11A)
    - Reference Library - Dept. (Box A36-11A)
    - Researchers 1991-1992 Nov (Box A36-11A)
    - S - General - RBD 1987-1991 (Box A36-11A)
    - S - General 1990 (Box A36-11A)
    - S - General - MSS 1991 (Box A36-11A)
    - Santayana 1990-1991 (Box A36-11A)
    - Schmidt, William (Box A36-11A)
    - Scott, Sen. Hugh 1989-1991 (Box A36-11A)
    - Security (Box A36-11A)
    - Seibel, Fred - Cartoons 1989-1991 (Box A36-11A)
    - Settle, Mary Lee Tazewell 1990 (Box A36-11A)
    - Showalter, Jerry 1990 (Box A36-11A)
    - Smithsonian Institution (1990- ) (Box A36-11A)
    - Solinet Workshop (Box A36-11A)
    - Sons of the American Revolution 1990 (Box A36-11A)
    - Southern Broadcast Archives (Box A36-11A)
    - Special Collections Correspondence 1991-1992 (Box A36-11A)
    - SCD - Smoking Issue (Box A36-11A)
    - Special Purchases Procedures Forms (Box A36-11A)
    - Stack Shift (Box A36-11B)
    - Stein, Gertrude (1990- ) (Box A36-11B)
    - Stettinius, Edward R. 1990-1991 (Box A36-11B)
    - Stowe, Harriet Beecher (1990) (Box A36-11B)
    - Surveys (1992- ) (Box A36-11B)
    - T - General - MSS & RBD 1987-1991 (Box A36-11B)
    - Taylor Family - Harry B. 1990-1991 (Box A36-11B)
    - Telephones - Information, memos, etc. (Box A36-11B)
    - Telephone bills 1992-1993 (Box A36-11B)
    - Tennyson, Alfred L. 1991-1992 (Box A36-11B)
    - Theses and Dissertations 1990-1991 (Box A36-11B)
    - Tinker, William (Box A36-11B)
    - Transmittals 1991-1991 (Box A36-11B)
    - Travel (Box A36-11B)
    - Travel Vouchers - Abraham (Box A36-11B)
    - Travel Vouchers - Defibaugh (Box A36-11B)
    - Travel - Laura Endicott (Box A36-11B)
    - Travel - Riser (Box A36-11B)
    - Travel Vouchers - Sisson (folder empty) (Box A36-11B)
    - Travel Vouchers - Wear / Pardee (Box A36-11B)
    - Trist, Nicholas 1990-1991 (Box A36-11B)
    - Twain, Mark (Box A36-11B)
    - Twain, Mark (for former correspondence see Sam. Clemens) 1991 (Box A36-11B)
    - Twin Oaks Community 1990-1991 (Box A36-11B)
    - Tyman [Twyman] Family (Box A36-11B)
    - U - General - MSS & RBK 1987-1991 (Box A36-11C)
    - University Administration - Madison Hall, Rotunda, General, etc. 1990 (Box A36-11C)
    - University of Virginia Misc. Memos 1992 (Box A36-11C)
    - University of Virginia photos & prints 1990-1991 (Box A36-11C)
    - University Press of Virginia 1990-1991 (Box A36-11C)
    - V - General - MSS & RBK 1987-1991 (Box A36-11C)
    - Vice [Virginia Intralibrary Computer Enthusiasts] (Box A36-11C)
    - Valentine Museum 1990 (Box A36-11C)
    - Virginia Cemeteries (1990- ) (Box A36-11C)
    - VCRP - Virginia Colonial Records Project 1990-1992 (Box A36-11C)
    - Virginia Foundation for the Humanities & Public Policy (Box A36-11C)
    - Virginia Historical Society 1990-1991 (Box A36-11C)
    - Virginia Library & Information Network (Box A36-11C)
    - VPI (Box A36-11C)
    - Virginia State Library (Box A36-11C)
    - Virginia State Library and Archives 1990-1992 (Box A36-11C)
    - Virgo - Acquisitions (Box A36-11C)
    - W - General - MSS & RBK 1987-1991 (Box A36-11C)
    - Warner, John 1989-1992 (Box A36-11C)
    - White Burkett Miller Center 1990-1991 (Box A36-11C)
    - Whitman, Walt 1990-1991 (Box A36-11C)
    - Whitman - Garland 1990 (Box A36-11C)
    - William and Mary College (Box A36-11C)
    - Williams, Tennessee 1990 (Box A36-11C)
    - Womens Issues & History 1990-1992 (Box A36-11C)
    - X-Y-Z - General - MSS & RBK 1980-1991 (Box A36-11C)
    - ALA Rare Book Conference - general correspondence 1959 June (Box A36-11D)
    - Rare Book Manual - for ALA conference (Box A36-11D)
    - ALA Rare Book Conference -mailing list (Box A36-11D)
    - [ALA Rare Book Conference] - Registration Forms - Acceptances - paid (A - Z) (Box A36-11D)
    - [ALA Rare Book Conference] - dinners and panels (people who wish to attend) (Box A36-11E)
    - ALA Rare Book Conference - Further Action (Box A36-11E)
    - ALA Rare Book Conference - MacKay, etc. (Box A36-11E)
    - ALA Rare Book Conference - Articles concerning (Box A36-11E)
    - ALA Rare Book Conference - Tentative reservations made (Box A36-11E)